https://www.barnowltrust.org.uk/sitemap/cookie-policy/

Nestboxes
Where’s the best place for your Barn Owl nestbox?
Roosting & nesting places
Is your area suitable?
Southern Scotland
How much land?
How to check for injuries
Rescued owl care: Should I get help?
Report a dead and/or ringed owl
Thinking of keeping a captive Barn Owl?
You are here: Home › Sitemap › Cookie Policy
Cookie overview:
Like most websites, this site uses cookies – small bits of text which your web browser uses to store information and help us to give you a better experience.
In general, cookies are used to retain user preferences and settings, store payment information and provide anonymised tracking data to third party applications. As a rule, cookies will make your browsing experience better. However, you may prefer to disable cookies on this site and others. The most effective way to do this is to disable cookies in your browser. We suggest consulting the Help section of your browser or taking a look at the About Cookies website which explains how to manage your cookies.
Permission to use cookies:
If the settings in your browser (the software that you are using to view this website), are adjusted to accept cookies, and you continue to use our website, we take this to mean that you accept our use of cookies.
Should you wish to remove or not use cookies from our site you can learn more about this below, however doing so might mean that our site may not work as you would expect.
Cookies in use on this site:
Website function cookies
We use cookies to make our website work as you’d expect, including to:
Remember any settings and preferences during and between visits.
Improve the speed and security of the site.
Collect anonymised stats which we use to improve our website, making it more useful, easier to navigate, etc.
Remember if you have accepted our terms and conditions
Remember if you have accepted our cookies
Make our shopping basket and checkout work
Save you having to login to your account every time
Determine if you are logged in to your account or not
Make our forms work securely
There is currently no way to prevent these cookies being set other than to not use our site.
Account users:
If you have an account and you log in to this site, a temporary cookie is set to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
The personal information you provide in your account details is stored indefinitely. You can see, edit, or delete your personal information at any time. Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
Third party functions:
Our site, like most websites, includes functionality provided by third parties, such as embedded YouTube videos. Embedded content from other websites behaves in the same way as if you had visited the other website. These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
These cookies sometimes track your usage across different websites.
Disabling these cookies may break the functions offered by these third parties.
Our site includes the following which use cookies: (Please refer to the links below for more information.)
YouTube videos (Google)
Google Maps
PayPal payment button
Social media cookies
ShareThis provides lots of sharing buttons for social media
ShareThis Privacy Policy + opt out button
The privacy implications vary depending on the privacy settings you have set on social media networks.
Anonymous visitor statistics cookies
We use cookies to compile anonymous visitor statistics, such as how many people have visited our website, what type of technology they are using (e.g. P.C. or mobile device, which helps to identify when our site isn’t working as it should for particular technologies), how long they spend on the site, what pages they look at etc. This helps us to continuously improve our website. These so called “analytics” programs also tell us if , on an anonymous basis, how people reached this site (e.g. from a search engine) and whether they have been here before.
Our site includes the following which uses cookies:
JetPack
Google Analytics
WordPress
Turning cookies off:
You can switch cookies off by adjusting your browser settings to stop it from accepting cookies (Learn how here). You can usually also remove cookies previously set. Doing so may limit the functionality of this and most other websites as cookies are a standard part of most modern websites.
Opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites.
Share This Privacy Policy + opt out button.
If you have concerns about “spyware”, you may find that anti-spyware software – which automatically deletes any cookies considered to be invasive – is a better solution, rather than switching off all cookies in your browser.
The cookie information on this page was derived from content provided by Attacat Internet Marketing and CookieBot.
Privacy Policy
We use cookies on our website to help give you the best on-line experience. Find out more.Okay, thanks
